Vengeance cannot be denied.
The Duel is a western, drama film directed by Kieran Darcy-Smith.
A Texas Ranger investigates a series of
unexplained deaths in a town called Helena.
Abraham Brant, played by Woody Harrelson.
David Kingston, played by Liam Hemsworth.
Marisol, played by Alice Braga.
Isaac, played by Emory Cohen.
Naomi, played by Felicity Price.
General Calderon, played by José Zúñiga.
The Duel is a 2016 American Western film directed by
Kieran Darcy-Smith and written by Matt Cook.
The film stars Liam Hemsworth, Emory Cohen, Woody Harrelson, and Alice Braga.
The film was released for limited release and video on
demand on June 24, 2016, by Lionsgate Premiere.
It was released on DVD and Blu-Ray on August 23, 2016.
The tone is emotional.